douho.com 2014-06-27

# Privacy - Online Games Douho

**PRIVACY POLICY FOR DOUHO.COM  
**We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION  
** Any personal information that you provide to our web site shall stay absolutely safe, private, and secure. We do not resell personal information to outside sources.

When placing an order, our e-commerce provider will handle your personal information and keep it absolutely safe, private and secure. In fact, even we cannot access to your credit card information. Your personal information (excluding credit card data) is shared only with us and the author of the game (if applicable) for administration purposes. 

**INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY LOGGED  
** Like almost every other web site, our systems may log information including your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site.

**COOKIES  
** Our web site may use cookies to store information about your visits. In addition, during the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**EMAIL NEWSLETTER  
** Our newsletter is strictly run as an "opt-in" newsletter. We never send unsolicited emails.

**SECURITY  
** We have taken the appropriate steps and followed industry standards to secure any personal data stored by our systems.

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING  
** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [Click Here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**EXTERNAL LINKS  
** This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**CONTACTING OUR WEB SITE  
** If you have any comments or questions about this privacy statement or any other issues you can [contact us](mailto:onlinegameshq@gmail.com).
